Connection is everything.
The Visitor is a crime, drama, music film directed by Tom McCarthy.
A college professor travels to New York City to attend a conference
and finds a young couple living in his apartment.
Prof. Walter Vale, played by Richard Jenkins.
Tarek Khalil, played by Haaz Sleiman.
Zainab, played by Danai Gurira.
Mouna Khalil, played by Hiam Abbass.
Barbara, played by Marian Seldes.
Karen, played by Maggie Moore.
The Visitor (Finnish: Muukalainen) is a 2008 drama film
directed by Finnish director Jukka-Pekka Valkeapää.
It is a joint production of Finland, Estonia, Germany, and the UK.
The film explores themes of michigan, immigration,
illegal immigration, drum, search for meaning.
The tone is emotional.